LARRY NGUYEN

Email Larryn.devegmail.com

Website Larryn35.github.io

Phone 510.912.1235

Github Larryn35

SUMMARY

Self-taught iOS developer located in the San Francisco Bay Area. Passion for learning and developing quality apps with an appealing UI design in mind. Background in pharmacy with experience providing excellent customer service, collaborating with other healthcare providers, and utilizing clinical knowledge to ensure safe and effective use of medications.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Drug Names - iOS

A quiz and flash card app for learning the brand and generic names of 300 popular prescription and over-the-counter drugs. Tracks daily, weekly, and all-time stats for quizzes. Built with SwiftUI and Core Data.

Available on the App Store

Webpage:

https://larryn35.github.io/drugnames.html

Features:

- Searchable list of all 300 drugs
- Editable hint for each drug
- Customizable app appearance
- Light and dark mode support

Hello World - iOS

A real-time chat app built with SwiftUI and Firebase. Users can join or create their own rooms and chat with others.

Github:

https://github.com/larryn35/HelloWorld

Features:

- User authentication via email and password
- Store and fetch pictures selected from photo library or camera
- Track message timestamps and number of unread messages

SKILLS

Languages: Swift

Databases: Firebase, Core Data

Tools: Xcode, Visual Studio Code, Github

Design: Canva, Figma

Other: CSS/HTML, HIPAA-trained

LARRY NGUYEN

Email larryn.devegmail.com

Website larryn35.github.io

Phone 510.912.1235

Github Larryn35

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacy Intern

Hy-Vee Pharmacy | October 2018 - June 2020

- Reviewed prescriptions for accuracy and appropriateness
- Counseled patients on medication use, side effects, and drug-drug interactions
- Communicated with healthcare providers to resolve patient and medication concerns

Pharmacy Technician

CVS Pharmacy | December 2011 - June 2014

- Assisted in filling and dispensing of medications
- Performed inventory tasks such as ordering medications and returning expired, damaged, and recalled medications

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota College of Pharmacy

August 2014 - May 2018 Doctor of Pharmacy

University of California, Irvine

September 2007 – June 2011 Bachelor of Science in Biology Bachelor of Science in Chemistry

LICENSES

MN Pharmacist License #124181

Minnesota Board of Pharmacy Issue: 04/04/19 | Expire: 02/28/22